export const CodeQuestions = [{
        prompt: "1. Everything in React is a ......?",
        optionA: "Module",
        optionB: "Component",
        optionC: "Package",
        optionD: "Class",
        answer: "Component",
        number: "1",
    },
    {
        prompt: "2. In which directory React Components are saved?",
        optionA: "Inside js/components/",
        optionB: "Inside vendor/components/",
        optionC: "Inside external/components/",
        optionD: "Inside vendor/",
        answer: "Inside js/components/",
        number: "2",
    },
    {
        prompt: "3. How many elements does a react component return?",
        optionA: "2 Elements",
        optionB: "1 Element",
        optionC: "Multiple Elements",
        optionD: "None of These",
        answer: "Multiple Elements",
        number: "3",
    },
    {
        prompt: "4. What is state in React?",
        optionA: "A persistant storage.",
        optionB: "An internal data store (object) of a component.",
        optionC: "component",
        optionD: "class",
        answer: "An internal data store (object) of a component.",
        number: "4",
    },
    {
        prompt: "5.Which of the following is not one of the early “protocols,” or ways to use the Internet?",
        optionA: "Blogging",
        optionB: "Telnet",
        optionC: "Gopher",
        optionD: "FTP",
        answer: "Blogging",
        number: "5",
    },
    {
        prompt: "6. What is Babel?",
        optionA: "A transpiler.",
        optionB: "An interpreter",
        optionC: "A Compiler",
        optionD: "Both Compiler and Transpilar",
        answer: "Both Compiler and Transpilar",
        number: "6",
    },
    {
        prompt: "7. What does the webpack command do?",
        optionA: "Transpiles all the Javascript down into one file",
        optionB: "Runs react local development server.",
        optionC: "A module bundler",
        optionD: "Internet",
        answer: "A module bundler",
        number: "7",
    },
    {
        prompt: "8. What port is the default where the webpack-dev-server will run?",
        optionA: "3000",
        optionB: "8080",
        optionC: "3306",
        optionD: "3303",
        answer: "8080",
        number: "8",
    },
    {
        prompt: "9. What is ReactJS?",
        optionA: "Server side Framework",
        optionB: "User-interface framework",
        optionC: "A Library for building interaction interfaces",
        optionD: "None of These",
        answer: "A Library for building interaction interfaces",
        number: "9",
    },
    {
        prompt: "10. In React what is used to pass data to a component from outside?",
        optionA: "setState",
        optionB: "render with arguments",
        optionC: "props",
        optionD: "PropTypes",
        answer: "props",
        number: "10",
    },
]